Rampi Federico Daniel Full Stack Developer

federampi@gmail.com Cel.: +54 9 3772 459589 Paso de los Libres, Corrientes - Argentina.

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub

ABOUT ME

I'm a full stack developer, I have experience working with JavaScript, React, Redux, Express.js, among others. I consider myself a proactive person, responsible, with logical thinking, I do well working in a team because I believe that cooperation is the best method to solve problems and meet the objectives. I am a curious person, who is always reading different methods or ways to improve my code.

TECHNOLOGIES:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, React.js, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, Git y Github, Postman, Sequelize, PostgreSQL.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Pi Pokemon

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop a pokemon App that includes: pokemon search, pokemon detail display, filtering, sorting, paging and creation.
- For the development I used React, Redux, pure CSS for the Frontend and Node.js, Express for the Backend. Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize. <u>Repository</u> | <u>Deploy</u>

Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bank

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop an App-mobile that includes: searches, filtering, sorting, user registration, login with authentication, administrator panel, user profile, news, payment gateway and transfers, fixed term, buying and selling cryptocurrencies, mailing system, etc.
- For the development we used React Navite, CSS, Redux, Figma for the Frontend and Node.js with Express for the Backend. Database in PostgresSQL and Sequelize. JWT was used for authentication, Nodemailer for mailing and Stripe for card payments.
- In this project I worked on the Backend side, we worked using the SCRUM methodology where we used Trello to write down the tasks to be done.

Frontend repository | Backend repository | Demo

LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native

• Ingles: B1 Intermediate EF SET Certificate

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Full stack Developer

Bootcamp Soy Henry | Feb. 2022 – Ag. 2022 |

• 700 hours of theoretical and practical courses.

IT infrastructure technician

Instituto Superior De Formación Docente Profesor Agustín Gómez | Feb 2012 - Dic 2013

 Career focused on preventive and corrective maintenance of computers, both hardware and software, also focused on the installation and maintenance of computer networks.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Technical Support

Jan 2014 – Jul 2022

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Repair of desktop computers, notebook, etc. both hardware and software, installation of programs, like operating systems, office automation, etc.

Also back up files and also file recovery, installation of network cable (utp), installation of cameras, etc.

IT Technical Support | Intern at Paso de los Libres Customs Office

Ag. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Maintenance and installation of wired and wireless networks, repair of computer equipment, both software and hardware, repair of printers, etc.